# **Zbigniew Stolarski**

I am a Frontend Developer creating modern and responsive websites from scratch using top frontend frameworks. I am doing my best to create a user-oriented website that is accessible and with fast loading speed. I'm using my experience to pick the right tools to create a design that suits your specific requirement.

# **Work History**

2022-07

#### **Frontend Developer**

- present

Chimera Prime, Warszawa, Polska

https://www.chimeraprime.com/

Software development house

 Developing new features for existing web applications. I was the most focused on payment flow to make applications profitable. Techstack: React.js, Redux, Typescript, Javascript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, MaterialUI

2021-08

### **Frontend Developer**

- 2022-07

Esri Polska, Warsaw, Poland

https://www.esri.pl/

Global market leader in GIS

 Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.

2019-09 - 2021-07

#### Frontend Developer

InCore Service, Warsaw, Poland

www.incpraca.pl

Online job agency

- IncPraca app development
- Implementation of website mockups in Figma software.
- Implementation of dozens of website components in the Vue.js framework.
- · Testing of created components in the Jest framework.
- · Technologies and tools used in the project:
- Vue.js, Jest, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Webpack, jQuerry, Sass, Bootstrap, git, npm, GitHub, Gitea, Bitbucket, Jira, Slack, Visual Studio Code

## **Education**

2018-12 - 2019-05

Coders Lab, Warsaw, Poland

www.franchise.coderslab.com/en

- Coding Bootcamp: 320 hours
- React.js framework, API communication, Responsive Web Design

2012-10

#### **Automation Control and Robotics, Master of Science**

- 2018-02

Lodz University of Technology, Lodz, Poland

www.p.lodz.pl/en

# **Projects**

2022-03

Social App

https://fir-508b2.web.app/

Social media app



# **Personal Info**

**Phone** 

797896967

**Email** 

stolarskizbigniew93@gmail.com

Website

www.zbigniewstolarski.pl

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/ZbigniewCL

Citizenship

Polish

# **Skills**

Vue.js, React.js, Redux, Jest, HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, Webpack, jQuerry, Bootstrap, MaterialUI, git

#### Software

Visual Studio Code

Windows

Linux

MacOS

# Languages

English - B1

# **Hobby**

- Internet of Things
- · Arduino programming
- · Drone filming
- · Website Applications

Fully-featured social media application using React, Firebase, Redux, Express, and Material-UI.

#### 2021-01 Portfolio

- 2021-02 www.zbigniewstolarski.pl

This is a website about me. It contains all my projects and easy contact with me

- Created with Vue.js styled with Bootstrap.
- Contact form handled by a PHP file.

#### 2021-02 Pikachu Game

- 2021-03

www.zbigniewstolarski.pl/#/furryGame

The game is about catching Pikachu without hitting the edges of the board. The ability to work on arrays and objects was essential.

#### 2021-03 Game Of LIfe

- 2021-04

www.zbigniewstolarski.pl/#/gameOfLife

The game presents the process of cells reproduction. It is a zero-player game, meaning that its evolution is determined by its initial state, requiring no further input.